D. H. Baldwin Company Records
D. H. Baldwin Company Records
1884-1955
Baldwin Piano Company. Albright, James M.
60 linear ft.
Incorporated in 1898, the D.H. Baldwin Company manufactured grand, spinet, and upright pianos. Known as Baldwin Piano Company, 1954-1963. Collection contains business correspondence (1895-1930); administrative records, including ledgers, account books, and sales books of the company and its subsidiaries (1902-1954).
148827
Biographical History
From inauspicious beginnings in a small, upstairs room in Cincinnati, the D.H. Baldwin Company grew to be one of the largest manufacturers and suppliers of pianos and organs in the United States. Baldwin began his business career by selling a few pianos and organs to friends and former music students in 1862. Soon he was able to invest $2,000 to found the company which bears his name.
Baldwin and his partners, Lucien and Clarence Wulsin, A. A. Van Buren, and George W. Armstrong, Jr. opened branch offices in other cities outside of Cincinnati. In 1890, they were able to build their own factory, the Baldwin Piano Company, to manufacture pianos. To supplement this production, they received pianos from other suppliers.
In 1898, the Baldwin Piano Company was incorporated and the supply factories became a part of Baldwin's new company, the D. H. Baldwin Company. The Hamilton Organ Company and the Hamilton Piano Company, located in Chicago, and the Baldwin Piano Company and the Ellington Piano Company in Cincinnati, were some of the suppliers.
International recognition was accorded the "House of Baldwin" when it won the Grand Prix at the Paris Exposition in 1900 and Lucien Wulsin was decorated with the Cross of the Legion of Honor. It also won the Grand Prize at the St. Louis Exposition in 1904, and the Grand Prize at London in 1914. By 1913 Baldwin was exporting to 32 countries.
In the 1920s Baldwin expanded its product line to player pianos, and thanks to prudent planning by then-president Lucien Wulsin II, the company was able to weather the Depression. After a brief hiatus during World War II when its factories, like many others, were diverted to producing airplane parts, the company returned to a brisk business in musical instruments. In 1946 Baldwin introduced the first electronic organs, which were so successful that the company changed its name in 1953 to Baldwin Piano & Organ Company.
During the 1970s the company made a concerted effort to expand into the financial sector, acquiring savings & loan institutions, insurance companies and investment firms; by 1982 pianos represented only 3% of the company's business, and the following year excessive debt forced the company into bankruptcy. For the next twenty years the company struggled in and out of debt and changed hands several times, eventually being purchased by Gibson Guitar Corporation in 2001. The company operates today as a division of Gibson Guitar Corporation, and manufactures instruments under the Baldwin, Chickering, Wurlitzer, Hamilton, and Howard names.
Baldwin products have for many years been the instrument-of-choice for professional pianists, orchestras and concert venues across the United States and throughout the world. Baldwin is America's largest acoustic piano manufacturer and sells more pianos in the U.S. than any other manufacturer.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The D. H. Baldwin Company Records are divided into four groups.
The collection begins with a small amount of Correspondence, which contains correspondence between the Baldwin Piano Company and three other piano manufacturing firms. It includes incoming and outgoing correspondence of the Baldwin Piano Company with the Vesey Piano Company (1929-1930), which reveals an effort on the part of Mr. Vesey to persuade the Baldwin Piano Company to build and market a quality radio (circa 1928); the minutes of a presidential report at a Standard Piano Company meeting (1895); and the minutes of a Valley Gem Piano Company meeting (1895).
The majority of the material is found in the next two series, both of which contain ledgers, general journals, cash books, and sales books for their respective companies. The daily transactions, cash receipts and disbursements, and sales records of the various companies involved in the corporation are registered in the journals, cash, and sales books. The ledgers summarize these transactions as well as information concerning costs, revenues, production, investment, distribution and sales. These two series are explained in greater detail below.
The Baldwin Company represents the administrative and producing factors of the corporation, and is subdivided into general administrative records, supply department records, and subsidiary records.
General administrative records of the Baldwin Company contain the Secretary's office ledgers (1902-1915) and cash books (1906-1942). The ledgers include sundry accounts as well as all the capital stock entries. The cash books contain general entries of revenues and real estate rentals from the supply departments and subsidiaries, and expenses incurred by the Baldwin Company.
Supply department records of the Baldwin Company contain the records of the Cincinnati and Chicago Heights warehouses. Included in these are ledgers (1903-1938) showing manufacturing expenses, equipment, goods in process, and charges to subsidiaries; sales books (1904-1920) showing entries of the sale of piano parts to various subsidiaries; and cash journals (1903-1942).
Subsidiary records of the Baldwin Company contain the record books of the various companies that helped make pianos for the Baldwin Company at one time or another. The major subsidiary companies include the following:
Baldwin Piano Manufacturing Company, founded in 1890: ledgers (1895-1938) and cash books (1892-1938). Included are such interesting items as a notice of the Grand Prix Award at the Paris Exposition, volume 95; a memo concerning the name change of the company in 1913, volume 76; and a photograph and information concerning the death of D.H. Baldwin, volume 92.
Ellington Piano Company: ledgers and cash books (1893-1938) and a general journal (1903-1906). The general journal contains summary reports of shipments, balance sheets, comparative wage cost tables, reports of the president, as well as other summary reports. Notable among the ledgers is volume 106, which contains correspondence of Mr. Wulsin, a company president, concerning stockholders and volume III, which contains correspondence from Mr. Wulsin to his board of directors. Volume 125, a cash book, contains a letter and a memorial photograph of D.H. Baldwin.
Hamilton Organ Company (1891-1920) and Hamilton Piano Company (1897-1938): ledgers and cash journals, for the same dates, summarizing the daily activities of these two Chicago-based companies. Of note is the organizational memo pertaining to the Howard Piano Company in volumes 161 and 165.
Miscellaneous other subsidiaries: the Howard Piano Company records (1919-1934) consisting of ledgers and cash books; the Monarch Piano Company records (1898-1933) consisting of ledgers, a journal and a cash book; the Perry Lumber Company ledgers and cash journals (1906-1922) containing entries of sales to the supply factories and subsidiary companies of the Baldwin Company; the Sargent Piano Company records (1921-1922) consisting of a ledger and a cash journal; the Valley Gem Piano Company records (1895-1901) consisting of one ledger revealing limited accounts with the Ellington Piano Company and the Standard Piano Company.
The Baldwin Piano Company represents the sales and distribution factors of the corporation and is divided into general records (general office, sales department, advertising, wholesale and rental department, agents and dealers and phonograph sales records) and division records, including those of Chicago, Cincinnati, Dallas, Denver, Indianapolis, St. Louis, Southern, Eastern, and Export divisions.
General records comprise the company records, 1884-1955. One of these, volume 215, is a summary ledger which contains early financial statements, division of capital and profits among the partners, agreements, clippings and letters by and about Clarence Wulsin and D.H. Baldwin. Other company records include the sales department ledgers and cash books (1903-1942), summarizing the sales of all the divisions; the cash books (1916-1938) for the advertising work; the wholesale and retail ledgers (1906-1938); and the agents and dealers ledgers, account books, contingent commission books and individual salesmen books (1908-1943). The ledgers, journals, cash books and sales books of the phonograph business (1917-1931) for all the divisions were brought together under company records.
Division records cover the years 1903-1938 and the bulk of them represent the Cincinnati and Denver divisions. The transactions of the various divisions of the Baldwin Piano Company are recorded in the ledgers, cash books and sales record books of the Chicago (1926-1930), Cincinnati (1903-1938), Dallas (1913-1929), Denver (1903-1931), Detroit (1923-1929), Eastern (1915-1930), Indianapolis (1917-1921), St. Louis (1926-1929), Southern (1917-1924) and Export (1916-1938) divisions.
A small amount of Miscellaneous records grouped at the end of the collection consist of journals (1914-1938) and a ledger for the Ellington, Hamilton, and Baldwin Manufacturing Company (1930-1933).
Arrangement of the Collection
Within each division, volumes are arranged by type (e.g. cash books, ledgers) and then chronologically.
Subject and Genre Headings
Music; Business and Industry; Baldwin, D. H.; Wulsin, Clarence.; Wulsin, Lucien, -1912.; Baldwin Piano Company -- Archives.; Baldwin Piano & Organ Company -- Archives.; D. H. Baldwin Company -- Archives.; Business.; Piano makers -- United States.; Manufacturers -- United States.; Advertisements.; Cashbooks.; Correspondence.; Ledgers (account books); Sales records.; Business.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Lucien Wulsin, Dec. 1967.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - Vesey Piano Company, 1929-1930 (Box 1)
  - Baldwin Piano Company, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Standard Piano Company, 1895 (Box 1)
  - Valley Gem Piano Company, 1895 (Box 1)
- Baldwin Company
  - General Administrative Records
    - Secretary's ledger, 1902, Jan. - 1903, June (Volume 1)
    - Secretary's ledger, 1903, July - 1908, Dec. (Volume 2)
    - Secretary's ledger, 1909, Jan. - 1915, Jan. (Volume 3)
    - Cash book, 1906, July - 1912, Aug. (Volume 4)
    - Cash book, 1915, Feb. - 1919, Sept. (Volume 5)
    - Cash book, 1919, Oct. - 1926, June (Volume 6)
    - Cash book, 1926, July - 1934, June (Volume 7)
    - Cash book, 1934, July - 1942, Aug. (Volume 8)
  - Supply Department
    - Cincinnati
      - Ledger #1, 1903-1905 (Volume 9)
      - Ledger #2, 1906-1907 (Volume 10)
      - Ledger #3, 1908-1910 (Volume 11)
      - Ledger #4, 1911-1912 (Volume 12)
      - Ledger #5, 1913-1914 (Volume 13)
      - Ledger #6, 1915-1916 (Volume 14)
      - Ledger #7, 1916-1917 (Volume 15)
      - Ledger #8, 1918-1919 (Volume 16)
      - Ledger #9, 1920, Jan. - June (Volume 17)
      - Ledger #10, 1920, July - 1922, June (Volume 18)
      - Ledger #11, 1922, July - 1923, June (Volume 19)
      - Ledger #12, 1923, July - 1924, Dec. (Volume 20)
      - Ledger #13, 1925 (Volume 21)
      - Ledger #14, 1926 (Volume 22)
      - Ledger #15, 1927 (Volume 23)
      - Ledger #16, 1928 (Volume 24)
      - Ledger #17, 1929 (Volume 25)
      - Ledger #18, 1930 (Volume 26)
      - Ledger #19, 1931 (Volume 27)
      - Ledger #20, 1932-1934, June (Volume 28)
      - Ledger #21, 1934, July - 1938, Dec. (Volume 29)
      - Cash journal #1, 1903, Jan. - 1905, Nov. (Volume 30)
      - Cash journal #2, 1905, Dec. - 1909, June (Volume 31)
      - Cash journal #3, 1909, July - 1912, Sept. (Volume 32)
      - Cash journal #4, 1912, Oct. - 1914, Dec. (Volume 33)
      - Cash journal #5, 1915, Jan. - 1917, Jan. (Volume 34)
      - Cash journal #6, 1917, Feb. - 1918, Dec. (Volume 35)
      - Cash journal #7, 1919, July - 1920, June (Volume 36)
      - Cash journal #8, 1920, July - Dec. (Volume 37)
      - Cash journal #9, 1921, Jan. - 1922, June (Volume 38)
      - Cash journal #10, 1922, July - 1924, May (Volume 39)
      - Cash journal #11, 1924, June - 1925, Oct. (Volume 40)
      - Cash journal #12, 1925, Nov. - 1927, Feb. (Volume 41)
      - Cash journal #13, 1927, March - 1928, June (Volume 42)
      - Cash journal #14, 1928, July - 1929, Oct. (Volume 43)
      - Cash journal #15, 1929, Nov. - 1931, March (Volume 44)
      - Cash journal #16, 1931, April - 1932, May (Volume 45)
      - Cash book, 1932, June - 1935, Dec. (Volume 46)
      - Cash book, 1936, Jan. - 1941, Dec. (Volume 47)
      - Cash book, 1942, Jan. - 1942, Sept. (Volume 48)
      - Sales book #1, 1904, May - 1905, June (Volume 49)
      - Sales book #2, 1905, July - 1907, Dec. (Volume 50)
      - Sales book #3, 1908, Jan. - 1909, July (Volume 51)
      - Sales book #4, 1909, Aug. - 1910, Dec. (Volume 52)
      - Sales book #5, 1911, Jan. - 1912, Feb. (Volume 53)
      - Sales book #6, 1912, March - 1913, June (Volume 54)
      - Sales book #7, 1913, July - 1914, Dec. (Volume 55)
      - Sales book #8, 1915, Jan. - 1916, May (Volume 56)
      - Sales book #9, 1916, June - 1917, Sept. (Volume 57)
      - Sales book #10, 1917, Oct. - 1918, Dec. (Volume 58)
      - Sales book #11, 1919, Jan. - 1920, Jan. (Volume 59)
      - Sales book #12, 1920, Feb. - Oct. (Volume 60)
    - Chicago Heights
      - Ledger, 1920-1921 (Volume 61)
      - Ledger, 1922-1923 (Volume 62)
      - Ledger, 1924-1925 (Volume 63)
      - Ledger, 1926-1928 (Volume 64)
      - Ledger, 1929-1930 (Volume 65)
      - Ledger, 1931, Jan. - June (Volume 66)
      - Cash journal, 1920, Sept. - 1924, Aug. (Volume 67)
      - Cash journal, 1924, Sept. - 1929, May (Volume 68)
      - Cash journal #1, 1929, June - 1931, June (Volume 69)
  - Subsidiary records
    - Baldwin Piano Manufacturing Company
      - Ledger #2, 1895, Jan. - 1896, Dec. (Volume 70)
      - Ledger #3, 1897, Jan. - 1899, Dec. (Volume 71)
      - Ledger #4, 1900, Jan. - 1901, Dec. (Volume 72)
      - Ledger #5, 1902, Jan. - 1905, Dec. (Volume 73)
      - Ledger #6, 1906, Jan. - 1909, Dec. (Volume 74)
      - Ledger #7, 1910, Jan. - 1912, Dec. (Volume 75)
      - Ledger #8, 1913, Jan. - 1914, Dec. (Volume 76)
      - Ledger #9, 1915 (Volume 77)
      - Ledger #10, 1917, Jan. - 1918, June (Volume 78)
      - Ledger #11, 1919-1920 (Volume 79)
      - Ledger #12, 1921-1922 (Volume 80)
      - Ledger #13, 1923-1924 (Volume 81)
      - Ledger #14, 1925-1926 (Volume 82)
      - Ledger #15, 1927-1928 (Volume 83)
      - Ledger #16, 1929-1931 (Volume 84)
      - Ledger #17, 1932-1935 (Volume 85)
      - Ledger #18, 1936, Jan. - July (Volume 86)
      - Ledger #1, 1936, Aug. - 1938, Dec. (Volume 87)
      - Daily record journal, 1911, Jan. - 1918, Feb. (Volume 88)
      - Sundry cost journal, 1921, Nov. - 1923, Feb. (Volume 89)
      - Cash journal, 1890, Aug. - 1891, May (Volume 90)
      - Cash journal #1, 1892, Jan. - 1897, Feb. (Volume 91)
      - Cash journal #2, 1897, March - 1900, Sept. (Volume 92)
      - Cash journal #3, 1900, Oct. - 1901, Dec. (Volume 93)
      - Cash journal #1, 1902, Jan. - 1904, Dec. (Volume 94)
      - Cash journal #2, 1905, Jan. - 1909, May (Volume 95)
      - Cash journal #3, 1909, June - 1913, June (Volume 96)
      - Cash journal #4, 1913, July - 1915, Aug. (Volume 97)
      - Cash journal #5, 1915, Sept. - 1917, Dec. (Volume 98)
      - Cash journal #6, 1918, Jan. - 1921, Feb. (Volume 99)
      - Cash journal #7, 1921, March - 1922, Dec. (Volume 100)
      - Cash journal #8, 1923, Jan. - 1925, Dec. (Volume 101)
      - Cash journal #9, 1926, Jan. - 1929, May (Volume 102)
      - Cash journal #10, 1929, June - 1936, July (Volume 103)
      - Cash journal #1, 1936, Aug. - 1938, June (Volume 104)
    - Ellington Piano Company
      - Ledger #1, 1893-1896 (Volume 105)
      - Ledger #2, 1897-1898 (Volume 106)
      - Ledger #3, 1899-1901, June (Volume 107)
      - Ledger #4, 1901, July - Dec. (Volume 108)
      - Ledger #5, 1902-1903 (Volume 109)
      - Ledger #6, 1904-1905 (Volume 110)
      - Ledger #7, 1906-1908 (Volume 111)
      - Ledger #8, 1909-1912 (Volume 112)
      - Ledger #9, 1913-1916 (Volume 113)
      - Ledger #10, 1917-1919 (Volume 114)
      - Ledger #11, 1920-1922 (Volume 115)
      - Ledger #12, 1923-1924 (Volume 116)
      - Ledger #13, 1925-1926 (Volume 117)
      - Ledger #14, 1927-1928 (Volume 118)
      - Ledger #15, 1929-1931 (Volume 119)
      - Ledger #16, 1932-1935 (Volume 120)
      - Ledger #17, 1936, Jan. - July (Volume 121)
      - Ledger #18, 1936, Aug. - 1938, Dec. (Volume 122)
      - General journal, 1903, June - 1906, June (Volume 123)
      - Cash journal #1, 1893, Jan. - 1898, June (Volume 124)
      - Cash journal #2, 1898, July - 1901, Dec. (Volume 125)
      - Cash journal #3, 1902, Jan. - 1906, Aug. (Volume 126)
      - Cash journal #4, 1906, Sept. - 1910, Dec. (Volume 127)
      - Cash journal #5, 1911, Jan. - 1915, Dec. (Volume 128)
      - Cash journal #6, 1916, Jan. - 1919, Dec. (Volume 129)
      - Cash journal #7, 1920, Jan. - 1922, Dec. (Volume 130)
      - Cash journal #8, 1923, Jan - 1925, June (Volume 131)
      - Cash journal #9, 1925, July - 1927, Nov. (Volume 132)
      - Cash journal #10, 1927, Nov. - 1931, April (Volume 133)
      - Cash journal #11, 1931, May - 1936, July (Volume 134)
      - Cash journal #1, 1936, Aug. - 1938, June (Volume 135)
    - Hamilton Organ Company
      - Ledger, 1891, June - 1892, Dec. (Volume 136)
      - Ledger, 1893, Jan. - 1896, Jan. (Volume 137)
      - Ledger, 1896, Jan. - 1898, Jan. (Volume 138)
      - Ledger, 1898, Feb. - 1901, June (Volume 139)
      - Ledger, 1901, Feb. - 1903, Feb. (Volume 140)
      - Ledger, 1906, Jan. - 1907, June (Volume 141)
      - Ledger, 1907, July - 1909, Dec. (Volume 142)
      - Ledger, 1910-1911 (Volume 143)
      - Ledger, 1912-1913 (Volume 144)
      - Ledger, 1914-1915 (Volume 145)
      - Ledger, 1916-1917 (Volume 146)
      - Ledger, 1818-1919 (Volume 147)
      - Cash journal, 1891, June - 1892, Oct. (Volume 148)
      - Cash journal, 1892, Nov. - 1894, Dec. (Volume 149)
      - Cash journal, 1895, Jan. - 1897, April (Volume 150)
      - Cash journal, 1897, May - 1900, May (Volume 151)
      - Cash journal, (General office), 1900, June - 1903, Feb. (Volume 152)
      - Cash journal, 1901, Feb. - 1903, Feb. (Volume 153)
      - Cash journal, 1905, March - 1906, Jan. (Volume 154)
      - Cash journal, 1906, Dec. - 1907 (Volume 155)
      - Cash journal, 1908-1909 (Volume 156)
      - Cash journal, 1910, Jan. - 1912, Oct. (Volume 157)
      - Cash journal, 1912, Nov. - 1916, Aug. (Volume 158)
      - Cash journal, 1916, Sept. - 1920, Aug. (Volume 159)
    - Hamilton Piano Company
      - Ledger, 1897, July - 1901, Jan. (Volume 160)
      - Ledger, 1901, Feb. - 1902, Dec. (Volume 161)
      - Ledger, 1903 (Volume 162)
      - Ledger, 1904 (Volume 163)
      - Ledger, 1905 (Volume 164)
      - Ledger, 1906-1907 (Volume 165)
      - Ledger, 1908-1909 (Volume 166)
      - Ledger, 1910-1911 (Volume 167)
      - Ledger, 1912-1913 (Volume 168)
      - Ledger, 1914-1915 (Volume 169)
      - Ledger, 1916-1917 (Volume 170)
      - Ledger, 1918-1919 (Volume 171)
      - Ledger, 1920-1921 (Volume 172)
      - Ledger, 1922-1923 (Volume 173)
      - Ledger, 1924-1925 (Volume 174)
      - Ledger, 1926-1928 (Volume 175)
      - Ledger, 1929-1930 (Volume 176)
      - Ledger, 1931, Jan. - 1938, Nov. (Volume 177)
      - Cash journal, 1901, Feb. - 1903, June (Volume 178)
      - Cash journal, 1903, July - 1905, Feb. (Volume 179)
      - Cash journal, 1906-1907 (Volume 180)
      - Cash journal, 1908-1909 (Volume 181)
      - Cash journal, 1910, Jan. - 1912, June (Volume 182)
      - Cash journal, 1912, July - 1914, Dec. (Volume 183)
      - Cash journal, 1915-1917 (Volume 184)
      - Cash journal, 1918, Jan. - 1921, April (Volume 185)
      - Cash journal, 1921, May - 1924, June (Volume 186)
      - Cash journal, 1924, July - 1927, Aug. (Volume 187)
      - Cash journal, 1927, Sept. - 1930, April (Volume 188)
      - Cash journal, 1930, May - 1935, Dec. (Volume 189)
    - Howard Piano Company
      - Ledger, 1919, May - 1926, March (Volume 190)
      - Ledger, 1926, April - 1936, Feb. (Volume 191)
      - Cash book, 1919, June - 1928, Dec. (Volume 192)
      - Cash book, 1929, Jan. - 1934, Nov. (Volume 193)
    - Monarch Piano Company
      - Ledger #1, 1910, April - 1924, Dec. (Volume 194)
      - Ledger, 1926, Jan. - 1938, Nov. (Volume 195)
      - Journal, 1898, April - 1901, Jan. (Volume 196)
      - Cash book (Volume 197)
    - Perry Lumber Company
      - Ledger of shipments, 1907, July - 1908, Jan. (Volume 198)
      - Pine Apple Sundry accounts, 1907, Nov. - 1909, April (Volume 199)
      - Ledger #1, 1907 (Volume 200)
      - Ledger #2, 1908-1909 (Volume 201)
      - Ledger #3, 1910-1911 (Volume 202)
      - Ledger #4, 1912 (Volume 203)
      - Ledger #5, 1913-1916 (Volume 204)
      - Ledger #6, 1917, Jan. - 1921, June (Volume 205)
      - Ledger #7, 1921, July - 1922, June (Volume 206)
      - Cash journal, J.S. Bennett account, 1907, Jan. - 1909, Feb. (Volume 207)
      - Cash journal #1, 1906, Aug. - 1910, June (Volume 208)
      - Cash journal #2, 1910, July - 1913, Jan. (Volume 209)
      - Cash journal #3, 1913, Feb. - 1916, July (Volume 210)
      - Cash journal #4, 1916, Aug. - 1920, May (Volume 211)
    - Sargent Piano Company
      - Ledger #1, 1921, June - 1922, June (Volume 212)
      - Cash journal, 1921, June - 1922, Dec. (Volume 213)
    - Valley Gem Piano Company
      - Ledger, 1895, Oct. - 1901, Dec. (Volume 214)
- Baldwin Piano Company
  - General records
    - Office
      - Summary ledger, 1884, June - 1907, June (Volume 215)
      - Ledger #1, 1914, Jan. - 1917, May (Volume 216)
      - Ledger #2, 1917, June - 1920, Aug. (Volume 217)
      - Ledger #3, 1920, Sept. - 1925, Dec. (Volume 218)
      - Ledger #4, 1926-1930 (Volume 219)
      - Ledger #5, 1931-1936 (Volume 220)
      - Ledger #6, 1937, Jan. - 1938, June (Volume 221)
      - Ledger, 1938, Jan. - 1943, Dec. (Volume 222)
      - Ledger, 1951-1953 (Volume 223)
      - Ledger, 1954-1955 (Volume 224)
    - Sales department
      - General ledger #1, 1903, July - 1905, Dec. (Volume 225)
      - General ledger #2, 1906-1907 (Volume 226)
      - General ledger #3, 1908-1910 (Volume 227)
      - General ledger #6, 1920, Aug. - 1930, Dec. (Volume 228)
      - General ledger #7, 1931, Jan. - 1942, June (Volume 229)
      - General office cash #8, 1910, Jan. - 1911, June (Volume 230)
      - General office cash #13, 1923, Jan. - 1926, June (Volume 231)
      - General office cash #14, 1926, July - 1930, June (Volume 232)
      - General office cash #15, 1930, July - 1935, Nov. (Volume 233)
      - General office cash #16, 1935, Dec. - 1941, Dec. (Volume 234)
    - Advertising
      - Advertising cash #4, 1916, Aug. - 1918, Sept. (Volume 235)
      - Advertising cash #5, 1918, Oct. - 1921, March (Volume 236)
      - Advertising cash #6, 1921, April - 1923, April (Volume 237)
      - Expense cash #3, 1920, June - 1923, April (Volume 238)
      - General and advertising cash #7, 1923, May - 1925, Feb. (Volume 239)
      - General & advertising cash #8, 1925, March - 1927, May (Volume 240)
      - General & advertising cash #9, 1927, June - 1929, May (Volume 241)
      - General & advertising cash #10, 1929, June - 1931, March (Volume 242)
      - General & advertising cash #11, 1931, April - 1933, Sept. (Volume 243)